

AHMAD RAZA

App Developer

About Me

I'm a Flutter Developer. I had started coding since 2020 and become a professional developer in 2022. I have great interest in coding, logic building and Requirements engineering. In short logics inspire me. I had worked in Coding Solution 24 and developed a bundle of apps there else that I had developed other apps. I had believe in myself if I want to do something then I'll complete it. I'm very hardworking.



03083180084



https://github.com/bagga16



linkedin.com/in/ahmad-razakahloon



ahmedbaggall6p@gmail.c om

Language

- English
- Urdu
- Panjabi

Skills

- IOS Development
- Android Development
- Flutter
- Dart
- Fire Base
- SDLC
- Java
- Basic Web Development

Experience

05/2022 - Present Coding Solution 24 (01/2022 - Present) App Developer (Job)

Coding Solution 24 (06/2022 - 05/2022) App Developer (Internship)

Achievements/Tasks

- As a App Developer I had Developed four Apps Till now.
 The Taxi Booking App including three Apps (User Side,
 Driver Side and Admin Side). Provide the facility to book a taxi for yourself or someone else in advance. Google maps and online Payments are integrated. Saves time.
- Beautiful UI of Medical Appointment Booking App.
- Let's Chat is a chating app I had developed using firebase. provide secure Conversation. Avoid third party involvement.
- Google maps integration in an app and performed multiple operations on it.

Contact: M. Afzaal Ali - 03004526367

ORGANIZATIONS

ITEC Society

KFUEIT Rahim Yar Khan 09/2022 - Present I had worked for my society as a Information Secretary.

Education

BS Information Technology

KFUEIT Rahim Yar Khan 08/2020 - Present

Interests

App Development 100%

Coding 100%

Logic Building 100%

Requirement engineering 100%